A Guide to the Letters of Ellen Glasgow to Arthur Glasgow 1905-1939
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Letters of Ellen Glasgow to Arthur Glasgow 1905-1939
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5347
This collection consists of 49 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift to the Library by Mr. Leslie Johnson, 80 Middle Road, Palm Beach, FL, on 1 Mar 1956.
Scope and Content Information
Glasgow writes regarding her personal life and financial difficulties during the Great Depression. Also included is a poem by Glasgow dated France, 1916; and a typescript citation of Glasgow, 1930 June 10, by H.W. Chase, University of North Carolina.
Arrangement
The letters are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- 1905 Mar. 27, photocopy
- 1906 Apr. 15, photocopy
- 1907 Aug. 14, photocopy
- 1908 Jul. 23, photocopy
- 1908 Aug. 10, photocopy
  Hotel des Alpes
- 1916 Jul. 4, photocopy
  date answered
- 1916 Jul. 4, photocopy
  Saturday, Richmond
- 1916 Jul. 4, photocopy
  Friday, Richmond
- 1916 Jul. 4, photocopy
  Sunday, Chestnut Hill
- 1916, typed, photocopy
  France, Poem by Ellen Glasgow
- 1918 Mar. 26, photocopy
- 1919 Oct. 11, photocopy
- 1920 Aug. 2, photocopy
- 1921 Dec. 27, typed, photocopy
- 1922 Jan. 5, photocopy
- 1923 Feb. 16, typed, photocopy
- 1923 Feb. 16, typed, photocopy
- 1923 Nov. 4, photocopy
- 1923 Nov. 16, typed, photocopy
- 1925 May 23, typed, photocopy
- 1925 May. 25, photocopy
- 1926 Jul. 28, typed, photocopy
- 1927 Feb. 18, typed, photocopy
- 1927 Apr. 11, typed, photocopy
- 1927 May 5, typed, photocopy
- 1930 Jan 11, typed, photocopy
- 1930 Feb 1, typed, photocopy
- typescript of citation of Ellen Glasgow by H.W. Chase, University of North Carolina 1930 Jun 10, photocopy
- 1930 Dec. 30, typed, photocopy
- 1931 Jun. 19, typed, photocopy
- 1931 Jun. 22, typed, photocopy
- 1931 Dec. 16, typed, photocopy
- 1931 Dec. 16, typed, photocopy
- 1932 Jan. 7, typed, photocopy
- 1932 Jan 7, typed, photocopy
- 1932 Mar. 5, typed, photocopy
- 1932 Feb. 26, typed, photocopy
  New York
- 1933 Jun. 17, photocopy
- 1933 Jul. 21, typed, photocopy
- 1935 Feb. 7, typed, photocopy
- 1935 Jul. 13, typed, photocopy
- 1935 Jul. 16, photocopy
- [1935] Oct. 5, photocopy
- 1935 Dec. 10, photocopy
- 1936 Feb. 18, typed, photocopy
- 1936 Mar. 17, typed, photocopy
- 1936 Oct. 3, typed, photocopy
- n.d., typed, photocopy
  Ventnor, New Jersey
- 1937 Jul. 1, photocopy
- [1939] Jul 7, typed, photocopy